<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>交换机迁移 - 标签 - 未来网络技术实验室</title>
        <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/%E4%BA%A4%E6%8D%A2%E6%9C%BA%E8%BF%81%E7%A7%BB/</link>
        <description>交换机迁移 - 标签 - 未来网络技术实验室</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>zh-CN</language><managingEditor>yongliu@hznu.edu.cn (FNTL)</managingEditor>
            <webMaster>yongliu@hznu.edu.cn (FNTL)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:26:56 &#43;0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/%E4%BA%A4%E6%8D%A2%E6%9C%BA%E8%BF%81%E7%A7%BB/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>BSM-LP: Bidirectional Switch Migration with Controller Load Prediction for Software-Defined Internet of Things.</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/bsm-lp/</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2024 18:26:56 &#43;0700</pubDate><author>
        <name>FNTL</name>
    </author><guid>http://localhost:1313/bsm-lp/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[摘要The Software-Defined Internet of Things (SD-IoT) utilizes the centralized control and programmability of SoftwareDefined Networking (SDN) to enhance network performance optimization and efficient resource utilization in IoT. As the network scale expands, the multiple-controller architecture becomes crucial for ensuring reliability and scalability in SD-IoT. However, the dynamic changes in traffic patterns often lead to imbalanced loads among controllers. Existing solutions primarily focus on switch migration schemes,]]></description>
</item><item>
    <title>Highly-Efficient Switch Migration for Controller Load Balancing in Elastic Optical Inter-Datacenter Networks</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/hesm/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 19:24:57 &#43;0600</pubDate><author>
        <name>FNTL</name>
    </author><guid>http://localhost:1313/hesm/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[摘要In elastic optical inter-datacenter networks, multiple software-defined networking (SDN) controllers have been used to improve scalability and reliability. The static controller deployment faces the problem of controller load imbalance under dynamic changes in network traffic. In response to this problem, existing research works proposed to use dynamic switch migration to achieve the controller load balancing. However, the efficiency of the existing switch migration is low, because the]]></description>
</item></channel>
</rss>
